Takaaki.
This is my order.
Deal a fatal blow to my father's company.
Understood.
As long as I don't use violence,
I can use any means necessary
to crush it completely, right?
Of course.
No need to show any mercy.
You can handle this, right?
Yeah.
"The Servant Prince" (Episode 8)
Yes.
If you leave the entire strategy to us,
yes, we guarantee you'll win the bid.
We're counting on you, then.
Got it.
That's all for now.
I won't let you have your way.
Excuse me.
President.
Regarding Goto Construction's core system,
It seems it's still riddled with bugs.
Their technical debt has
ballooned out of control.
I hear it's gotten to the point where
no company dares to take it on.
I figured as much.
They already lost their
credibility due to the data leak.
To think they still haven't
found a way to bounce back.
Yes.
How is the station building
project coming along?
Ah, about that.
Just as you predicted, President,
the bidding is merely a formality.
In reality, Goto Construction has
already been chosen behind closed doors.
If they knew about Goto
Construction's current internal situation,
this deal would fall through, too.
Next, we just need to set up a competitor
to replace Goto Construction.
And have them
successfully enter the bidding.
Understood.
Any other orders?
Orders?
This order is the most
fired up I've ever been.
Excuse me?
Never mind. I was just talking to myself.
Understood.
I'll take my leave now.
I've always wanted
to lock Naoya up.
So that I would be the
only thing in his world.
That's right.
Like keeping a frail little bird in a cage.
Maybe that's what would give
me the most peace of mind.
But Naoya stood up on his own two feet.
I...
I'm going to get a part-time job.
And then, he flew out of
that room full of energy.
We'll be living here starting today.
Just the two of us.
The Naoya I could lock in my embrace
is no longer here.
Good morning.
Are you okay?
I just feel...
So powerless.
Huh?
I tried negotiating with upper
management after that, but it was no use.
Even though Mori-san said
after he gets back from his trip abroad,
he'd be willing to come back to
work under the re-employment system.
In the end, a store manager is
nothing more than an on-site coordinator.
Just one word from the
higher-ups at headquarters,
and this store we worked so hard
to build up together,
can be taken away in an instant.
Manager.
I'm truly sorry.
Wait, why are you apologizing?
This isn't your fault, Goto-kun.
I'm really grateful to you.
Please, raise your head.
Anyway,
Until we close down,
please keep working hard with us.
I'm counting on you.
Manager...
Manager, I haven't given up yet.
Since it's come to this,
let's prove it to them with our sales.
Huh?
Let's make our sales and reviews
number one among all the branches.
Goto-kun...
He's right.
I'll show them the kitchen's grit, too.
I'll keep providing the best service
right down to the very last customer.
Let's make headquarters regret
ever wanting to close such a great store.
Everyone...
Manager.
Let's show them what we're made of.
Yeah.
All right, let's leave the
higher-ups speechless.
Yeah, let's do this!
Let's give it our all!
Here is your dessert,
our seasonal cake.
Please enjoy.
I can't just bark orders at Takaaki.
I have to do everything in my power, too.
- Would you like me to pour this for you?
- Yes, please.
Certainly. Excuse me.
Yes, right away.
Thank you for waiting.
Nishida, just add the
demi-glaze sauce and it's done.
Got it.
Regarding the restaurant
"Luore" and Unicolla,
[Goto Construction]
Both are proceeding according
to your instructions, President.
I see.
However, President,
Is this really okay?
What?
Nothing.
Tanizawa.
If you have the free
time to talk back to me,
You'd be better off securing
a system vendor to replace Unicolla.
If the system isn't fixed, our
company's credibility can't be restored.
Yes, sir.
Besides, this is a critical
moment before the bidding.
The issue with the system,
keep a tight lid on it.
It absolutely must not leak to the outside.
Understood.
I see.
That station building
project is, to my dad...
No... to Goto Construction,
it's their biggest lifeline.
If we strike there,
we can deal them a fatal blow.
Hit them hard.
Understood.
I'll execute it flawlessly.
Ah...
Yuma.
I figured this was the case.
You figured it out?
Figured out that Father was behind this.
Yeah.
But honestly,
I never thought he'd go this far.
After all, before getting in my way,
As the top executive, shouldn't he figure
out how to manage his own company first?
That just shows how much
Father cares about you.
Huh?
Father must be terrified of your abilities.
If he lets you do as you please,
You'll definitely achieve
greater things than him.
He wants to stop that from happening.
To keep you from succeeding, he deliberately
pushes difficult problems onto you.
He wants to make you submit to him.
He wants to keep you
close so he can watch you.
It's a terrifying obsession.
It's enough to make your skin crawl.
In contrast, I've only ever been
treated as your replacement.
Someone like me...
Is just a tool he uses to provoke you.
Even though I'm a part of the company, too,
Father refuses to listen to a word I say.
Father is wrong right now.
Everyone in the company is fed up, too.
Morale is falling apart.
Yuma, do you remember the
subsidiary I used to manage?
Right before they went bankrupt, I used my final
authority to transfer them back to headquarters.
They will definitely
be a great help to you.
Go gather your allies, Yuma.
Build your own faction.
To stand up against our dad.
Then come back, brother.
Those people are your allies, right?
Please.
I'm at my limit doing this alone.
No.
I'm not going back.
That's how it is.
I'm going to live my life with him.
Right, Takaaki?
Yeah, of course.
It'll be fine.
You can definitely do it.
The one to shoulder the future of
Goto Construction is you, Yuma.
After that,
Thanks to the competitor
Takaaki arranged entering the bid,
Goto Construction hit rock bottom.
Why?
Why did it turn out like this?
That station building project
was already internally decided to be ours.
Our company's system
vulnerabilities still haven't been fixed.
That's the root of it all.
That's why I said we
needed to handle it ASAP.
But President, the only ones who can rebuild
that massive system in a short time...
Is Unicolla. We have no other choice.
So,
Which company beat us to the bid?
It was Amagi Construction.
By the way, intelligence indicates that
Their system maintenance has
already been handed over to Unicolla.
That guy's company again?
Furthermore, led by your
younger brother Yuma,
the anti-president faction
has banded together.
As the company's performance deteriorated,
Dad's unifying power completely collapsed.
And as for the restaurant "Luore,"
Thanks to everyone,
our sales ranked number one.
That's great!
We really showed them what we're made of.
Yes.
I have one more thing to report.
This store...
Has been confirmed to stay open.
(Notice of Store Closure Cancellation)
Really?
That's amazing!
Thank goodness!
However, in exchange, the Mita branch,
which has seen declining sales recently,
Will be merged into our store.
Then our understaffing issue...
Will be solved.
Thank you all so much.
Goto-kun.
It's all thanks to you not giving up.
I really appreciate it.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Let's keep working hard together.
Mori-san will be back soon, too.
Yeah.
Alright, everyone together.
Ready?
Let's do this!
Anyway,
the restaurant can stay open.
That's wonderful news.
Yuma has been working really hard, too.
He took the lead in forming a new faction.
I heard all the top employees, especially
the younger ones, are following him.
I see.
Dad probably doesn't have
a single ally left by his side.
It's going to be the era of a brand new
Goto Construction built by Yuma.
Yeah, he'll definitely do a great job.
Takaaki, thank you so much.
No.
I only acted
because of your orders.
Your orders mean everything to me.
They are my reason for living.
Takaaki.
Yeah.
So that's how it is.
Two grown men acting like this.
How disgraceful.
Those words.
I'll return them right back to you.
What?
Mom was the only one
who thought of you that way.
The only one who found your
pathetic behavior endearing.
No one will ever feel
that way about you again.
Never again.
Blinded by short-term gains,
you neglected cybersecurity.
As the leader of an organization,
it seems you've completely lost sight of
what you should truly be protecting.
What does a nouveau
riche brat like you know?
I offered you such a high price.
Why did you refuse?
You were the one who canceled the contract
in the first place, President Goto.
Did you really think
the person you cast aside
would still lend you a helping hand now?
Please.
Help me.
At this rate,
everything I've built...
Goto Construction is going to go bankrupt.
Please.
I'm begging you.
I refuse.
Because I only take orders from him.
Go visit my mother's grave first.
And apologize for everything you've done.
If you do that, I'll ask him to help.
Understood.
Enjoy your meal.
I plan to take over Goto Construction
properly in Dad's place.
Because your allies
are all on my side.
Having such reliable partners
is all thanks to you.
No.
It's because you worked so hard.
That's why everyone is following you.
They are now officially
your allies.
Yuma.
You're right.
You now have a one-of-a-kind,
invincible expert
backing you up.
I can't afford to lose either.
Yeah.
Maybe so.
An invincible expert?
That's what Yuma said.
He said you are
one of a kind to me.
No.
I'm not that amazing.
But the moment you took over the system,
Dad's bankrupt company
came back to life.
So maybe Yuma was right.
I'll be counting on you from now on.
My very own expert.
Yeah, I understand.
Can I ask you something?
Why did you order me
to save his company?
Don't you hate your father
from the bottom of your heart?
Yeah.
I hate him.
Even now.
But rather than sending
him straight to hell,
I wanted him to choose
a more painful way to live.
Even if the company is rebuilt,
I want him to live all alone
and taste absolute despair.
Mom is no longer by his side.
He single-handedly destroyed the only
person who loved him unconditionally.
I hope this becomes Dad's
most irreversible regret.
That might indeed be
the cruelest punishment.
Yeah.
I won't end up like Dad.
So, Takaaki,
please stay by my side forever.
Understood.
Hey.
This isn't one of my usual orders.
I want to hear your true feelings.
I know.
I want to be with you forever, too.
With you, Naoya.
Yeah.
Can I give you an order?
Of course.
You've been working too hard.
Take some time off
and go on a trip with me.
Understood.
Alright.
Takaaki, let's go.
Okay.
Is camping okay for our trip?
Yeah.
Deep in the mountains
where there's zero cell service.
Huh?
If there's a signal, you'll
just end up working again.
Okay.
Today, we're going to
eat camp food together.
Then, we'll take our time
talking by the campfire.
Understood.
Yeah.
Oh?
What's wrong?
Be careful.
Sorry.
(Special Episode Preview)
Takaaki, make the rain stop.
Stop the rain.
Oh, that's nice.
This is absolutely amazing.
It feels great being the only one
who knows his hidden side.
You've truly met a wonderful person,
Goto-san.